Privacy Policy - Wikiwand
=========================

Wikiwand (WikiPele LTD) provides an Internet site and mobile application with a modern interface that optimizes the content available on Wikipedia ([www.wikipedia.org](https://www.wikipedia.org/)) for a quicker and significantly improved reading experience (the “**Site**”). Wikiwand respects your right to privacy. Your ability to make informed choices about the uses of your information is important to us. This privacy policy details how we collect, use and store information and data that we receive. If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policies, please contact us at privacy@wikiwand.com.

As used in this privacy policy, “**Personal Information**” means information that can be directly associated with a specific person or entity such as a name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. Other terms capitalized but not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Service, a current version of which is available at [https://www.wikiwand.com/terms](https://www.wikiwand.com/terms) (the “**Terms**”).

### Information We Collect

In order to use the Site, you may be prompted to log in through a social network or provide specified information. If you log in through a social network, such as Facebook, we will receive such Personal Information about you as is provided by such social network. Please check the policies of such social network in order to understand what information we receive. If you create an account with us, we receive and store all information that you provide in the creation of the account.

We also collect information when you make use of the Site, including your browsing history. The Site will also record certain information automatically, such as your IP address, mobile device or computer, operating system and browser. In addition, we collect any information you provide when you contact us for any reason. You are not required by law to provide us with any such information, but by using the Site and agreeing to the Terms you agree to provide us with such information.

We may use services such as Google Analytics or other analytics services that provides us with analysis of the use of our Site.

### How We Use Information

We will not share your Personal Information with third parties without your explicit permission, except when required by law, regulation, subpoena or court order or as otherwise expressly set forth herein. We may use Personal Information and other information internally – for example, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to make the Site more useful for you and for our other customers.

By analyzing all information we receive, we may compile statistical information across a variety of users (“**Statistical Information**”). Statistical Information helps understand trends and customer needs so that new services can be considered and so the Site and associated services can be tailored to customer desires. We may share Statistical Information with our partners, pursuant to commercial terms that we determine in our sole discretion. In addition, we may provide any information to third parties, so long as we have removed any information that identifies any specific individual or user, such as a name, address or contact information.

### How we Protect Information

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will delete any Personal Information provided to us by a user upon the receipt of a written request by such user. We cannot restore information once it has been deleted.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of text that is sent to a visitor's browser. The browser provides this piece of text to the device of the originating visitor when this visitor returns. A “persistent” cookie may be used to help save your settings and customizations across visits. Most Web browsers are initially configured to accept cookies, but you can change this setting so your browser either refuses all cookies or informs you when a cookie is being sent. Also, you are free to delete any existing cookies at any time. Please note that some features of the Site may not function properly when cookies are disabled or removed.

### Third Party Sites and Services

We are not responsible for the use of any data by third parties, and we cannot vouch for the privacy policies of any third party. The Site may link to or use web sites or services belonging to third parties. We have no control over third-party sites or services, and all use of third-party sites or services is at your own risk. We cannot accept responsibility for the privacy policies of any such sites. We are not responsible for content available by means of such sites or services. We do not endorse any services or offered by third parties and we urge our users to exercise caution in using third-party sites or services.  When we provide information to third parties, we remove any information that identifies any particular individual or user, such as a name, address or contact information, but we cannot provide complete assurance that the recipient will not be able to associate such de-identified information with a particular individual.  
  
The Site may contain links to third party content provided or sponsored by Outbrain. Please see the privacy policy of such third party content provider, available at [http://www.outbrain.com/privacy](https://www.outbrain.com/privacy) in order to understand how it collects, uses and stores your data.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 14. In the event you become aware that an individual under the age of 14 has enrolled without parental permission, please advise us immediately.

### Other Uses or Transfer of Your Information

We will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing us to disclose the identity or behavior of any user suspected to have engaged in illegal behavior.

We may use subcontractors that are located in countries other than your own, and send them information we receive. For example, we may send your information to any countries outside the United States, Canada or the European Union. All our subcontractors will be subject to non-disclosure and non-use obligations. Nevertheless, some countries may have levels of protection of personal and other information which are not as high as in your country of residence or business.

We may transfer our databases containing information if we sell our business or part of it.

### Changes

We may update this privacy policy from time to time, and we encourage you to review it periodically.

### Comments and Questions

If you have any comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at privacy@wikiwand.com.

Chrome & Firefox top rated extension

Enjoying Wikiwand?
------------------

Give good old Wikipedia a great new look
